var quizEnglish1 = [
  {
    question: "	I’d like to	_____ a reservation.",
    choices: ["	Book	", " make	", " form	", "set"],
    correct: " make	",
  },
  {
    question: "	Mary <u>can swim very well</u>",
    choices: [
      "	Likes swimming best of all",
      "	Practices swimming every day",
      " Is good at swimming",
      " Feels good when she goes swimming",
    ],
    correct: " Is good at swimming",
  },
  {
    question: "	<u>I’m free</u> this afternoon",
    choices: [
      "	Can do anything",
      " Have time",
      " Will see you",
      " Will stay home",
    ],
    correct: " Have time",
  },
  {
    question: "	Mai _____	a white shirt today",
    choices: [" Is wearing", "	Is putting on", "	Wears", "	Puts on"],
    correct: " Is wearing",
  },
  {
    question: "	The moon cake is _____	nice.",
    choices: ["	Too", "	Such", "	Much", " Very"],
    correct: " Very",
  },
  {
    question: "	A: _______ B: He sits on the left side.",
    choices: [
      "	Where is the left side",
      "	Where is Mile sitting",
      " Where does Mike sit",
      " Who is on the left side",
    ],
    correct: " Where does Mike sit",
  },
  {
    question: "	A: Excuse me. Is there a station near here? B:_______",
    choices: [
      "	It’s near",
      "	It’s not near here",
      " No, there isn’t",
      " Not much",
    ],
    correct: " No, there isn’t",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	A: I’m sorry I don’t know. You’ d better ask that policeman over there.B:_______",
    choices: ["	I’m sorry too", " Thank, anyway", " Excuse me", " Yes, I will"],
    correct: " Thank, anyway",
  },
  {
    question: "	A:______	B: Let me show you on the map.",
    choices: [
      "	Do you have a map",
      "	Where can you find a map",
      "	Where do you live in the USA",
      "	Can you tell me how to do it",
    ],
    correct: "	Where do you live in the USA",
  },
  {
    question: "	A:______ B: it’s January 2nd ,2005",
    choices: [
      "	What is today",
      "	What is the day today",
      " What is the date today",
      " Is today Sunday",
    ],
    correct: " What is the date today",
  },
  {
    question: "	Where is the_______post office, please?",
    choices: ["	Near", "	Nearest", "	Close", "	Closest"],
    correct: "	Nearest",
  },
  {
    question: "	We always <u>begin</u> our lesson at eight",
    choices: ["	Have", "	Like", " Start", " Prepare"],
    correct: " Start",
  },
  {
    question: "	My uncle is <u>not here</u>",
    choices: ["	Out of town", " Away", " On holiday", " There"],
    correct: " Away",
  },
  {
    question: "	You must <u>leave</u> now",
    choices: ["	Finish", "	Be ready", " Start", " Prepare"],
    correct: " Start",
  },
  {
    question: "	Mary is <u>short</u>.",
    choices: ["	Not thin", " Not tall", " Not big", " Not weak"],
    correct: " Not tall",
  },
  {
    question: "	I hope you can come to________party next Saturday",
    choices: [" My", "	Me", "	If’s", "	Mine"],
    correct: " My",
  },
  {
    question: "	The boy_______football now.",
    choices: ["	Play", "	Plays", "	Is playing", "	Is going to play"],
    correct: "	Is playing",
  },
  {
    question: "	There________a ball under the bed",
    choices: ["	Has", "	Have", " Is", " Are"],
    correct: " Is",
  },
  {
    question: "	His brother works in___________office",
    choices: ["	A", " An", " The", " <>"],
    correct: " An",
  },
  {
    question: "	Her work starts________half past eight.",
    choices: ["	For", "	On", " At", " With"],
    correct: " At",
  },
  {
    question: "	Wan is from_______",
    choices: ["	Chinese", "	American", "	Japanese", " Canada"],
    correct: " Canada",
  },
  {
    question: "	It’s very cold in winter. It’s best_________	warm clothes",
    choices: [" To wear", "	We wear", "	Wearing", "	When to wear"],
    correct: " To wear",
  },
  {
    question: "________Beautiful car it is!",
    choices: [" What a", "	What", "	How", "	How a"],
    correct: " What a",
  },
  {
    question: "	In spring the trees turn ________",
    choices: [" Green", "	Yellow", "	Dark", "	Red"],
    correct: " Green",
  },
  {
    question: "	There are no <u>classes</u> on Sundays",
    choices: ["	Schools", " Lessons", " Classrooms", " Classmates"],
    correct: " Lessons",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	It’s getting late and we have to <u>be up</u> early in the morning.",
    choices: ["	Put on", "	Get dressed", "	Wake up", " Get up"],
    correct: " Get up",
  },
  {
    question: "	We had <u>a good time</u> on the farm last week.",
    choices: [
      "	Were pleased",
      "	Enjoyed ourselves",
      "	Felt good",
      "	Laughed a lot",
    ],
    correct: "	Enjoyed ourselves",
  },
  {
    question: "	There is____________red apple in her hand",
    choices: ["	An", " A", " The", " <>"],
    correct: " A",
  },
  {
    question: "	My father reads newspapers for__________every evening.",
    choices: ["	A half hour", "	Half hour", "	Half a hour", " Half an hour"],
    correct: "	Half an hour",
  },
  {
    question: "	Our English teacher often helps me_________________my English",
    choices: ["	At", "	In", "	With", "	For"],
    correct: "	With",
  },
  {
    question: "	You really should look after____________",
    choices: ["	You", "	Your", "	Yours", "	Yourself"],
    correct: "	Yourself",
  },
  {
    question: "	You’d	_________ go there.",
    choices: ["	Not better", "	Better don’t", " Better not", " Better not to"],
    correct: " Better not",
  },
  {
    question: "	Let Mary___________the work",
    choices: [" Do", "	Does", "	Did", "	Doing"],
    correct: " Do",
  },
  {
    question: "	Keep the window____________	, please",
    choices: ["	Close", "	Closed", "	Closing", "	To close"],
    correct: "	Closed",
  },
  {
    question: "	Now I can speak	______________English.",
    choices: ["	A few", "	Few", "	A little", "	Little"],
    correct: "	A little",
  },
  {
    question: "	The boys enjoy____________football very much",
    choices: [" Playing", "	Play", "	To play", "	Plays"],
    correct: " Playing",
  },
  {
    question: "	Two of them are here. But where are ________________	students?",
    choices: ["	Other", "	Another", "	Others", "	The other"],
    correct: "	The other",
  },
  {
    question: "	A: How _____ are these apples? B: 3 dollars a pound",

    choices: ["	Well", " Much", " Cost", " Price"],
    correct: " Much",
  },
  {
    question: "	Look, the children_____________their exercise now.",
    choices: ["	Do", "	Does", "	Did", "	Are doing"],
    correct: "	Are doing",
  },
  {
    question: "	Thank you for ______________	me.",
    choices: [
      " Coming to see",
      "	Come to see",
      "	Come to seeing",
      "	Coming and see",
    ],
    correct: " Coming to see",
  },
  {
    question: "	It’s time	______ have a rest",
    choices: ["	To", "	Should", "	That", "	So to"],
    correct: "	To",
  },
  {
    question: "	I don’t like this box. Please ___________	",
    choices: ["	Bring to me", " Take it away", " Bring it here", " Take it off"],
    correct: " Take it away",
  },
  {
    question: "	The teacher told John__________	in class",
    choices: ["	Not talk", "	Not to talk", "	To not talk", "	Not talking"],
    correct: "	Not to talk",
  },
  {
    question: "	My aunt was ill. I had to____________	her",
    choices: ["	Look at", "	Look for", " Look after", " Look into"],
    correct: " Look after",
  },
  {
    question: "	Is there anything wrong____________	your bike?",
    choices: ["	At", "	For", " With", " To"],
    correct: " With",
  },
  {
    question: "You must go to see a doctor ________ you are ill.",
    choices: ["That", "When", "Then", "Before"],
    correct: "When",
  },
  {
    question: "Can you carry this box ________ yourself?",
    choices: ["About", "By", "With", "At"],
    correct: "By",
  },
  {
    question: "They came at last ________.",
    choices: ["At once", "The latest", "In the end", "Late"],
    correct: "In the end",
  },
  {
    question:
      "My mother told me to look ________ the baby carefully when she was away.",
    choices: ["To", "After", "For", "At"],
    correct: "After",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Jimmy was ________ young to understand what had happened to his parents.",
    choices: ["So", "Such", "Too", "That"],
    correct: "Too",
  },
  {
    question: "The boy threw the coin ________ the river.",
    choices: ["On", "Into", "Below", "Under"],
    correct: "Into",
  },
  {
    question: "She wanted to get a job; ________ she needed money very much.",
    choices: ["So", "For", "With", "To"],
    correct: "For",
  },
  {
    question: "Why do you want ________ your job there?",
    choices: ["Leave", "To leave", "Leaving", "For leaving"],
    correct: "To leave",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I'd like to get more experience ________ learn about different kinds of work.",
    choices: ["Of", "With", "But", "And"],
    correct: "And",
  },
  {
    question: "Can you work on Saturday afternoons ________ we need you?",
    choices: ["If", "But", "And", "Because"],
    correct: "If",
  },
  {
    question: "I ________ swim. Would you like to come?",
    choices: ["Will", "Am going for a", "Go for", "Have gone"],
    correct: "Am going for a",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Tommy ________ in Florida for five years but now he ________ in Texas.",
    choices: [
      "Lives/lives",
      "Lived/lives",
      "Lives/living",
      "Was living/has lived",
    ],
    correct: "Lived/lives",
  },
  {
    question: "Melinda ________ when she ________ the strange animal.",
    choices: [
      "Scream/see",
      "Screamed/saw",
      "Screamed/seeing",
      "Screams/seeing",
    ],
    correct: "Screamed/saw",
  },
  {
    question: "Tell me what ________.",
    choices: ["I should say", "Should I say", "Should say", "To have said"],
    correct: "I should say",
  },
  {
    question: "Kim is much ________ Nathan.",
    choices: ["So tall than", "Taller than", "Tall than", "As tall as"],
    correct: "Taller than",
  },
  {
    question: "Call me when you ________ there.",
    choices: ["Reach", "Reached", "Will reach", "Should reach"],
    correct: "Reach",
  },
  {
    question: "Paul lived here from 1980 to 1990. He ________ live there.",
    choices: ["Lives", "Is used to", "Used to", "Uses to"],
    correct: "Used to",
  },
  {
    question: "I don’t like horror films: They’re too ________.",
    choices: ["Frightened", "Fightening", "Excited", "Exciting"],
    correct: "Fightening",
  },
  {
    question: "She ________ on the phone when he walked in.",
    choices: ["Talks", "Has talked", "Had talked", "Was talking"],
    correct: "Was talking",
  },
  {
    question: "Terry is a pilot, but he ________ at the moment.",
    choices: ["Has not flown", "Does not fly", "Did not fly", "Isn’t flying"],
    correct: "Isn’t flying",
  },
  {
    question:
      "At 7 pm tomorrow, Martha ________ waiting for you at the Rex Hotel.",
    choices: ["Will", "Has been", "Will be", "Would be"],
    correct: "Will be",
  },
  {
    question: "The vegetables do not look ________ to me!",
    choices: ["Fresh", "Freshly", "Freshable", "Freshing"],
    correct: "Fresh",
  },
  {
    question:
      "____________I don’t like her, I have to admit that she is a fast worker.",
    choices: ["Although", "Because", "Nevertheless", "However"],
    correct: "Although",
  },
  {
    question: "I felt very tired, ________ I went straight to bed.",
    choices: ["Because", "Although", "So", "When"],
    correct: "So",
  },
  {
    question: "I will have my car ________ next week.",
    choices: ["Service", "Servicing", "'s service", "Serviced"],
    correct: "Serviced",
  },
  {
    question: "The trouble with John is that he never stops ________.",
    choices: ["Talk", "Talks", "Talked", "Talking"],
    correct: "Talking",
  },
  {
    question: "“What a pity you failed!” - “Yes, I wish I ________ it better.”",
    choices: ["Do", "Did", "Had done", "Have done"],
    correct: "Had done",
  },
  {
    question: "Daisy has been learning Portuguese ________ a long time.",
    choices: ["<>", "Since", "For", "As"],
    correct: "For",
  },
  {
    question: "While Mark was feeding his cat, the doorbell ________.",
    choices: ["Ring", "Rings", "Rang", "Has rung"],
    correct: "Rang",
  },
  {
    question: "They began to realize the dangers ________ smoking.",
    choices: ["In", "On", "With", "Of"],
    correct: "Of",
  },
  {
    question: "Human beings are always afraid ________ dying.",
    choices: ["Of", "For", "At", "In"],
    correct: "Of",
  },
  {
    question: "Alice is never kind ________ any of us.",
    choices: ["To", "With", "At", "From"],
    correct: "To",
  },
  {
    question: "John was good, but Steve was even ________.",
    choices: ["More", "Gooder", "Better", "Best"],
    correct: "Better",
  },
  {
    question: "Peter was one of the best ________ of his generation.",
    choices: ["Acts", "Acting", "Actors", "Acted"],
    correct: "Actors",
  },
  {
    question: "Here’s the ________, sir. - Thank you. I’ll pay by credit card.",
    choices: ["Money", "Banknote", "Currency", "Bill"],
    correct: "Bill",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Billy is a playboy. I guess you can always find him at ________.",
    choices: ["The casino", "Home", "The office", "School"],
    correct: "The casino",
  },
  {
    question: "The job is so dangerous that there is only one ________ for it.",
    choices: ["Appliance", "Applicator", "Applier", "Applicant"],
    correct: "Applicant",
  },
  {
    question: "She <u>occasionally</u> reads a novel.",
    choices: ["Sometimes", "Usually", "Rarely", "Seldom"],
    correct: "Sometimes",
  },
  {
    question: "Mary doesn’t like doing the <u>washing-up.</u>",
    choices: [
      "Washing her clothes",
      "Washing her hair",
      "Cleaning the house",
      "Washing the dishes",
    ],
    correct: "Washing the dishes",
  },
  {
    question: "All of these are fruit EXCEPT",
    choices: ["Oranges", "Pears", "Onion", "Apples"],
    correct: "Onion",
  },
  {
    question: "Can I ________ in here for the ANZ Airway flight to Can Tho?",
    choices: ["Go", "Examine", "Check", "Pass"],
    correct: "Check",
  },
  {
    question:
      "If your luggage weighs more than 25 kilos, you’ll have to pay an excess baggage ________.",
    choices: ["Money", "Penalty", "Charge", "Punishment"],
    correct: "Charge",
  },
  {
    question: "Where is she? She has gone to ________.",
    choices: ["Movie", "Cinema", "Church", "Home"],
    correct: "Church",
  },
  {
    question: "The car <u>fantastic</u>. I love it.",
    choices: ["Fast", "Expensive", "Economical", "Wonderful"],
    correct: "Wonderful",
  },
  {
    question: "We have no ________ but to continue our work.",
    choices: ["Chance", "Choice", "Way", "Escape"],
    correct: "Choice",
  },
  {
    question: "I have to go now. I have a ________ with my girlfriend at nine.",
    choices: ["Day", "Date", "Reservation", "Booking"],
    correct: "Date",
  },
  {
    question:
      "With good sense of direction, you won’t get ________ in the shopping mall.",
    choices: ["Hurt", "Lost", "Ill", "Mad"],
    correct: "Lost",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Could you tell me what ________ you are eating? It seems very delicious to me.",
    choices: ["Kind", "Disk", "Style", "Dish"],
    correct: "Dish",
  },
  {
    question: "If you ________ too much TV, you will get poor grades again.",
    choices: ["Watch", "Enjoy", "Relax", "Have"],
    correct: "Watch",
  },
  {
    question:
      "There was something ________ with our computer. I cannot print this document.",
    choices: ["Wrong", "<>", "Difficult", "Unknown"],
    correct: "Wrong",
  },
  {
    question:
      "How many students will take ________ in the speaking contest tomorrow?",
    choices: ["Past", "Place", "Park", "Part"],
    correct: "Part",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The manager has promised to ________ the problem as soon as he can.",
    choices: ["Solve", "Deal", "Take", "Roll"],
    correct: "Solve",
  },
  {
    question:
      "My father likes to collect coins from  <u>different</u> countries.",
    choices: ["Many", "Faraway", "Various", "Neighbouring"],
    correct: "Various",
  },
  {
    question: "That job__________ requires a lot of patience and hard work.",
    choices: ["Applies", "Involves", "Insists", "Asks"],
    correct: "Involves",
  },
  {
    question: "Unlike running, volleyball and football are ___ sports.",
    choices: ["Collection", "Union", "Team", "Group"],
    correct: "Team",
  },
  {
    question: "What perfume are you wearing___, Miss Smith?",
    choices: ["Having", "Wearing", "Putting", "Taking"],
    correct: "Wearing",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Lord Worth wanted Mary to ___ a special effort because Sir Thomas is a very important guest.",
    choices: ["Do", "Make", "Try", "Give"],
    correct: "Make",
  },
  {
    question: "He ___ his living by repairing clocks.",
    choices: ["Makes", "Does", "Acquires", "Gets"],
    correct: "Makes",
  },
  {
    question: "He was too tired to____ working.",
    choices: ["Refuse", "Stop", "Stay", "Continue"],
    correct: "Continue",
  },
  {
    question: "My sister ___ us that she had talked with Mike last night.",
    choices: ["Said", "Told", "Spoke", "Asked"],
    correct: "Told",
  },
  {
    question: "Take it easy. Don’t <u>rush</u>.",
    choices: ["Hurry", "Make a mess", "Push-in", "Run"],
    correct: "Hurry",
  },
  {
    question: "You needn’t shout. I am not____________.",
    choices: ["Deaf", "Debt", "Dead", "Doubt"],
    correct: "Deaf",
  },
  {
    question: "A man who is very healthy ______ needs to see a doctor.",
    choices: ["Should go", "Needs", "Ought", "Does not need"],
    correct: "Does not need",
  },
  {
    question: "The robber was ___ three days ago.",
    choices: ["Grasped", "Seized", "Arrested", "Handed"],
    correct: "Arrested",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The house, which is ____ half a million pounds, was sold last week.",
    choices: ["Cost", "Price", "Value", "Worth"],
    correct: "Worth",
  },
  {
    question: "Please ___the radio: I’m trying to concentrate.",
    choices: ["Slow down", "Take off", "Put down", "Put on"],
    correct: "Put down",
  },
  {
    question: "Why don’t you ____ your coat? It’s rather cold in here.",
    choices: ["Try on", "Take off", "Get off", "Put on"],
    correct: "Put on",
  },
  {
    question: "We aren’t ___ enough to purchase that luxury car.",
    choices: ["Poor", "Rich", "Strong", "Weak"],
    correct: "Rich",
  },
  {
    question: "The policemen <u>searched</u> the truck carefully.",
    choices: ["Looked for", "Examined", "Got on", "Left"],
    correct: "Examined",
  },
  {
    question: "These new jeans are so ____ that I cannot get them on.",
    choices: ["Tight", "Short", "Narrow", "Heavy"],
    correct: "Tight",
  },
  {
    question: "I’ve bought a <u>second-hand</u> computer.",
    choices: ["Very old", "Used", "Cheap", "Low-quality"],
    correct: "Used",
  },
  {
    question: "A: How ______ can Alice type? B:  52 words a minute.",
    choices: ["Good", "Much", "Quick", "Fast"],
    correct: "Fast",
  },
  {
    question:
      "There are too many cars and not ____ parking spaces in the city centre.",
    choices: ["A lot", "A few", "Enough", "A number of"],
    correct: "Enough",
  },
  {
    question:
      "He was dictating some letters to his secretary when the fire bell ______.",
    choices: ["Struck", "Rang", "Shook", "Shouted"],
    correct: "Rang",
  },
  {
    question: "The plane ___into the trees behind me.",
    choices: ["Hit", "Crashed", "Struck", "Collied"],
    correct: "Crashed",
  },
  {
    question: "The weather is really <u>awful</u> today.",
    choices: ["Fine", "Nice", "Strange", "Terrible"],
    correct: "Terrible",
  },
  {
    question: "John was ____ lucky to pass the examination.",
    choices: ["Comfortable", "Easy", "Envious", "Lucky"],
    correct: "Lucky",
  },
  {
    question: "The clerk was very <u>impolite</u> to the old customer.",
    choices: ["Dishonest", "Unhelpful", "Rude", "Unkind"],
    correct: "",
  },
  {
    question: "What would you like to do at the weekend?",
    choices: [
      "I like to do a lot",
      "I can’t stand it",
      "I’d like to see a football match",
      "I don’t like the weekend",
    ],
    correct: "I’d like to see a football match",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	The astronauts climbed down the ladder and stepped ___the planet",
    choices: ["	Into", "	Over", " Onto", " Above"],
    correct: " Onto",
  },
  {
    question: "	They have lived in Hanoi____20 years",
    choices: [" For", "	Until", "	Since", "	More than"],
    correct: " For",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	When I worked there I was bored ___	doing the same ting every day",
    choices: ["	By", "	of", "	with", "	About"],
    correct: "	with",
  },
  {
    question: "	Please don’t use the office phone ___	personal calls.",
    choices: ["	By", "	About", " For", " With"],
    correct: " For",
  },
  {
    question: "	Mark is always afraid ___	spiders",
    choices: ["	With", " Of", " by", " in"],
    correct: " Of",
  },
  {
    question: "	I don’t know	 ___ he’s married",
    choices: ["	At", "	About", "	With", " If"],
    correct: " If",
  },
  {
    question: "	___ 	He gets to the airport, he ‘ll let us know",
    choices: ["	Wherever", "	However", "	Although", " As soon as"],
    correct: " As soon as",
  },
  {
    question: "	When he ___	the plane, he	let us know",
    choices: ["	Left/will", "	Leaves/will", "	Leaves/would", "	Left/was"],
    correct: "	Leaves/will",
  },
  {
    question: "	The street was empty ___	Mrs.Riley",
    choices: ["	Despite", "	Except", "	Except for", "	Besides"],
    correct: "	Except for",
  },
  {
    question: "	Jack bought us ___ tea",
    choices: ["	A few more", "	Too many", "	A lot", "	Some more"],
    correct: "	Some more",
  },
  {
    question: "___	Can dance well.",
    choices: [
      "	These both children",
      "	Both of they",
      "	Both them",
      "	Both these girls",
    ],
    correct: "	Both these girls",
  },
  {
    question: "	Must we do it now? No, you _______ 	",
    choices: ["	Must", "	Needn’t", "	Did not need", "	Mustn’t"],
    correct: "	Needn’t",
  },
  {
    question: "	He’s a good guitarist, but he plays the piano____________",
    choices: ["	Also well", "	Too hardly", "	Very good", " Much better"],
    correct: " Much better",
  },
  {
    question: "	Aren’t they friends___	?",
    choices: [" Of yours", "	Of you", "	To yours", "	To you"],
    correct: " Of yours",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	The other car pushed my car into the car in front. In passive voice, it should read:",
    choices: [
      "	My car was pushed in front of the other car",
      "	My car is pushed into the orther car",
      "	My car was pushed into the car in front",
      "	My car is pushed by the other car",
    ],
    correct: "	My car was pushed into the car in front",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	We’ll have to find a new flat soon. In passive voice, it should read:",
    choices: [
      "	A new flat has to be found soon",
      "	A new flat must be found soon",
      "	A new flat is found soon",
      "	A new flat will have to be found soon",
    ],
    correct: "	A new flat will have to be found soon",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	‘Is the party almost over?”“I think so. A lot of people ______	to leave.”",
    choices: ["	Is beginning", "	Are beginning", "	Begin", "	Have beginning"],
    correct: "	Are beginning",
  },
  {
    question: "	“You look tired.”“I am. I have_____to do”",
    choices: [
      "	Too many homeworks",
      "	Too much homeworks",
      " Too much homework",
      " Too much homework assignments",
    ],
    correct: " Too much homework",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	“Did you have bad weather on the trip?”“Yes, we had	_____ rain than the weatherman had anticipated.",

    choices: ["	A lot of", "	A lot more of", " A lot more", " Many more"],
    correct: " A lot more",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	“Parachute jumping is a lot of fun”“ But it must be ___	to jump for the fitst time”",
    choices: [" Frightening", "	Frightened", "	Fright", "	Frighten"],
    correct: " Frightening",
  },
  {
    question: "	Brenda likes going to the theatre and____________",
    choices: [" So do I", "	So go I", "	So I like", "	So I am"],
    correct: " So do I",
  },
  {
    question: "	Budgies never speak	___ parrots",
    choices: ["	Well as", "	Better than", "	As good as", "	Well than"],
    correct: "	Better than",
  },
  {
    question: "	My little dog is only	___ your handbag",
    choices: [" As big as", "	Small as", "	Not as big as", "	Bigger as"],
    correct: " As big as",
  },
  {
    question: "	There’s	___ as quiet as a goldfish",
    choices: ["	None", "	Anything", " Nothing", " Whatever"],
    correct: " Nothing",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	To get over my headache, the doctor gave me some tablets and asked me to ___ tow with water two times a day.",
    choices: ["	Take", "	Drink", "	Get", "	Find"],
    correct: "	Take",
  },
  {
    question: "	How long will it___you to finish this?",
    choices: ["	Need", " Take", " Demand", " Want"],
    correct: " Take",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	If the customer	___not satisfied,please have him call the manager",
    choices: ["	Am", " Is", " Are", " Be"],
    correct: " Is",
  },
  {
    question: "	The plane will be landing	___ Chicago in twenty minutes",
    choices: ["	With", "	Into", " In", " For"],
    correct: " In",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	The seminar was canceled because the invitations were not	___ in time",
    choices: ["	Printer", " Printed", " Printing", " Print"],
    correct: " Printed",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	If the waiter cannot handle your request, the captain__	assist you.",
    choices: ["	Will", "	Has", "	Did", "	Is"],
    correct: "	Will",
  },
  {
    question: "	The meeting is postponed ___	Mr.Tan’s plane was late.",
    choices: ["	Although", "	While", " Because", " With"],
    correct: " Because",
  },
  {
    question: "	The training session has been changed from 8:30	___ 9:00",
    choices: ["	At", " To", " In", " By"],
    correct: " To",
  },
  {
    question: "	Are you	___ for the big test tomorrow?",
    choices: [" Prepared", "	Prepare", "	Alert", "	Watchful"],
    correct: " Prepared",
  },
  {
    question: "	 __	 It was Mr.Guiton’s birthday, his staff took him to luch.",
    choices: ["	Although", "	During", " Because", " That"],
    correct: " Because",
  },
  {
    question: "	This product	___our most popular item.",
    choices: [
      "	Always has considered been",
      "	Has been always considered",
      "	Has been considered always",
      " Has always been considered",
    ],
    correct: " Has always been considered",
  },
  {
    question: "	Is the annual report____________",
    choices: ["	Avail", "	Available", "	Availability", "	Availing"],
    correct: "	Available",
  },
  {
    question: "	The bell captain suggested that more porters___hire",

    choices: ["	Are", "	Have", " Be", " Do"],
    correct: " Be",
  },
  {
    question: "	The guard must	__ your identification at the gate.",
    choices: ["	Checked", "	Checking", "	Checks", " Check"],
    correct: " Check",
  },
  {
    question: "	Employees dislike tasks that are____________",
    choices: ["	Repeat", "	Repetitive", "	Repetition", "	Repetitively"],
    correct: "	Repetitive",
  },
  {
    question: "	Visitors are reminded___	name tags at all times",
    choices: [" To wear", "	Wear", "	Be worn", "	Is wearing"],
    correct: " To wear",
  },
  {
    question: "	If we had started earlier, we___	the deadline",
    choices: ["	Would meet", "	Would have met", "	Will meet", "	Will have met"],
    correct: "	Would have met",
  },
  {
    question: "	If Ms. Kamano leaves at 2:00, she___	at the station on time",
    choices: [
      "	Would have arrived",
      " Will arrive",
      " Arrived",
      " Would arrive",
    ],
    correct: " Will arrive",
  },
  {
    question: "	a letter for Mr. Cam was left ___	Mr. Brittoo’s desk",
    choices: [" Through", " On", " Out", " Up"],
    correct: " On",
  },
  {
    question: "	The CD-player was damaged when it____",
    choices: [
      " Was delivered",
      "	Has delivered",
      "	Was delivering",
      "	Had delivered",
    ],
    correct: "Was delivered",
  },
  {
    question: "	Mr. Hatori was very ___	when he got a promotion",
    choices: ["	Excite", "	Exciting", " Excited", " Excites"],
    correct: " Excited",
  },
  {
    question: "	The price of all cruises ____	airfare and all transfers",
    choices: ["	To include", " Includes", " Including", " Include"],
    correct: " Includes",
  },
  {
    question: "	Mr. Brett missed the plane ___	he was working late",
    choices: ["	After", "	Until", "	Because", "	And"],
    correct: "	Because",
  },
  {
    question: "	Many customers have repuested that they___	notice of our sales",
    choices: [" Receive", "	Receives", "	Received", "	Receiving"],
    correct: " Receive",
  },
  {
    question: "	The workers were loading the truck when the boxes____",
    choices: ["	Has fallen", "	Falls", " Fell", " Is falling"],
    correct: " Fell",
  },
  {
    question: "	The new manager,___ was just hired, will start tomorrow",
    choices: ["	She", "	He", "	Which", " Who"],
    correct: " Who",
  },
  {
    question: "	Mr. Kumar	____ if he had been delayed",
    choices: [
      "	Would call",
      "	Would have called",
      "	Will be calling",
      "	Will calling",
    ],
    correct: "	Would have called",
  },
  {
    question: "	The clerk ___	the computer manuak from the secretary",
    choices: ["	Lent", "	To loan", "	Loaned", "	Borrowed"],
    correct: "	Borrowed",
  },
  {
    question: "	Of all tour ships, this is out ___",
    choices: ["	more bigger", "	big", "	bigger", " biggest"],
    correct: " biggest",
  },
  {
    question: "	The purser got his assistant ___	the passenger orientation",
    choices: ["	Conducting", " To conduct", " Conducted", " Conducts"],
    correct: " To conduct",
  },
  {
    question: "	All travel arrangements must be completed	___ December 5",
    choices: ["	With", "	In", "	For", " By"],
    correct: " By",
  },
  {
    question: "	The bookcase is___	the door",
    choices: [" Beside", "	Among", "	Between", "	Across"],
    correct: " Beside",
  },
  {
    question: "	Ms. Mosley is___	member of our advertising team",
    choices: [
      "	Creative",
      "	Most creative",
      "	More creative",
      "	The most creative",
    ],
    correct: "	The most creative",
  },
  {
    question: "	Meeting are scheduled	___in the first floor auditorium",
    choices: ["	Always", "	Sometimes", "	Rarely", "	Every month"],
    correct: "	Every month",
  },
  {
    question: "	__ 5:00, the subway becomes very crowded",
    choices: ["	When", " After", " Since", " Until"],
    correct: " After",
  },
  {
    question: "	The airport was__	Mr. Debionne had expected",
    choices: ["	The busiest", " Busier than", " Busy as", " As busy"],
    correct: " Busier than",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	The personnel director screend the job applicants	___ arranging interviews",
    choices: ["	Because", "	Until", "	Since", " Before"],
    correct: " Before",
  },
  {
    question: "	The board of directors will meet __	October 10",
    choices: ["	For", "	To", " On", " In"],
    correct: " On",
  },
  {
    question: "	Ms. Nyen was giving her speech when the microphone ___",
    choices: ["	Is failing", "	Fails", "	Had failed", " Failed"],
    correct: " Failed",
  },
  {
    question: "	The status report	___ the financial projections were both late",
    choices: ["	Or", " And", " But", " Nor"],
    correct: " And",
  },
  {
    question: "	A firm will not __	if its employees are unhappy",
    choices: [" Prosper", "	Prosperous", "	Prosperity", "	Prospering"],
    correct: " Prosper",
  },
  {
    question: "	The intern ___ a fax machine before",
    choices: [
      "	Had used never",
      " Had never used",
      " Never had used",
      " Used had never",
    ],
    correct: " Had never used",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	If there __	some restaurants near the hotel, the tourist would not have to take taxis.",
    choices: ["	Were", "	Was", "	Will be", "	Would be"],
    correct: "	Were",
  },
  {
    question: "	Mid America Airlines’ flight __	Phonenix arrives at Gate 9",
    choices: [" From", "	In", "	By", "	On"],
    correct: " From",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	In the mornings the kitchen staff turns on the ovens and __ coffee",
    choices: ["	Brewing", "	Brew", " Brews", " Brewed"],
    correct: " Brews",
  },
  {
    question: "	The	__ speech made the audience restless",
    choices: [" Boring", "	Bored", "	Bores", "	Bore"],
    correct: " Boring",
  },
  {
    question: "	This year the annual meeting takes place __ Toronto",
    choices: ["	On", "	For", "	By", " In"],
    correct: " In",
  },
  {
    question: "	___ we were late,we could not enter the conference hall",
    choices: ["	Although", " Because", " Therefore", " However"],
    correct: " Because",
  },
  {
    question: "	If I ___ you, I would send the contract by courier",
    choices: ["	Am", "	Is", "	Was", " Were"],
    correct: " Were",
  },
  {
    question: "	Participants ___ fly to the convention can get a group rate",
    choices: ["	They", " Who", " Which", " Whom"],
    correct: " Who",
  },
  {
    question: "	Pens and stationery	___ kept in the top drawer",
    choices: [" Are", "	Is", "	Was", "	Am"],
    correct: " Are",
  },
  {
    question: "	The chief engineer is knowledgeable and __",
    choices: [" Industrious", "	Industry", "	Industrial", "	Industries"],
    correct: " Industrious",
  },
  {
    question: "	Ms. Neil	___the general manager of the hotel since 1994",
    choices: ["	Has", "	Has been", "	Had been", "	Had"],
    correct: "	Has been",
  },
  {
    question: "	The Message is ___	Mr. Moriwarki’s answering machine",
    choices: ["	In", "	Of", " On", " To"],
    correct: " On",
  },
  {
    question: "	Mr. Ross got the graphics department	the charts",
    choices: [" To prepare", "	Preparing", "	Prepare", "	Prepared"],
    correct: " To prepare",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	He __	the whole morning looking for the report, but still couldn’t find it",
    choices: ["	Brought", "	Passed", "	Had", " Spent"],
    correct: " Spent",
  },
  {
    question: "	  ___ That occasion you should lock the cab door",
    choices: ["	In", "	At", "	By", " On"],
    correct: " On",
  },
  {
    question: "	He said he’d dropped the key	___ a puddle",
    choices: ["	At", " In", " During", " For"],
    correct: " In",
  },
  {
    question: "	He’d just arrived home to find his wife ___	tears",
    choices: [" In", "	At", "	Through", "	By"],
    correct: " In",
  },
  {
    question: "	This advertisement was __	last week’s paper too",
    choices: ["	On", " In", " Over", " Above"],
    correct: " In",
  },
  {
    question: "	The man banged the glass down on the table and stared	__ me",
    choices: ["	Through", "	In", "	Over", " At"],
    correct: " At",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	The swimmer lay __	his back, closed his eyes, and relaxed in the water",
    choices: [" On", "	In", "	Through", "	Over"],
    correct: " On",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	When the Bishop stepped	__ the plane there were a lot of journalists and cameramen",
    choices: ["	Out", "	Outside", "	Down", " Off"],
    correct: " Off",
  },
  {
    question: "	She said she didn’t want to go	__ this excursion",
    choices: ["	At", "	By", "	With", " On"],
    correct: " On",
  },
  {
    question: "	006 woke up with his hands tied	__ his back",
    choices: ["	On", "	Through", "	Over", " Behind"],
    correct: " Behind",
  },
  {
    question: "	The wall was made	__thick glass",
    choices: ["	By", " Of", " Off", " In"],
    correct: " Of",
  },
  {
    question: "	“they all work hard.”“Which one works __	of all?”",
    choices: ["	Harder", "	The hardest", "	Most hard", "	The most hardly"],
    correct: "	The hardest",
  },
  {
    question: "	Listen to what I am saying,__	?",
    choices: ["	Don’t you", " Will you", " Do you", " Mind you"],
    correct: " Will you",
  },
  {
    question: "	If I could speak Spanish, I	__ next year studying in mexico.",
    choices: [" Would spend", "	Would have spent", "	Had spent", "	Will spent"],
    correct: " Would spend",
  },
  {
    question: "	__,he left for England to further his studies",
    choices: [
      "	Twenty years old",
      "	He was twenty years old",
      "	Having been twenty years old",
      " When he was twenty years old",
    ],
    correct: " When he was twenty years old",
  },
  {
    question: "	Nobody is ready to go,___?",
    choices: ["	Are they", "	Isn’t he", "	Is not he", "	Aren’t they"],
    correct: "	Are they",
  },
  {
    question: "	The package containing books and records __	last week",
    choices: [
      "	Is delivered",
      "	Are delivered",
      " Was delivered",
      " Were delivered",
    ],
    correct: " Was delivered",
  },
  {
    question: "	He went to prison ___	a car",
    choices: [
      "	By stealing",
      "	That he stole",
      " For stealing",
      " To have stolen",
    ],
    correct: " For stealing",
  },
  {
    question: "	__ be in class?",
    choices: [
      "	Haven’t you",
      "	Oughtn’t you",
      " Shouldn’t you",
      " Haven’t you got",
    ],
    correct: " Shouldn’t you",
  },
  {
    question: " Have a nice day!”“Thank you! _____ 	",
    choices: ["	And yours", "	The same to you", "	The same", "	A much to you"],
    correct: "	The same to you",
  },
  {
    question: "	You cannot make___",
    choices: [
      " People learn",
      "	People to learn",
      "	People learning",
      "	That people learn",
    ],
    correct: " People learn",
  },
  {
    question: "	Mrs. Chou,	____husband is a diplomat, gives cooking lessons.",
    choices: ["	Whom", "	Who", " Whose", " Who’s"],
    correct: " Whose",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	Seven other cars have withdrawn <u>due</u> to bad weather conditions.",
    choices: [" Owing to", "	At the time of", "	Right for", "	In spite of"],
    correct: " Owing to",
  },
  {
    question: "	He’s coming here to <u>take part in</u> a discussion program",
    choices: [" Participate", "	Take portion", "	Organize", "	Watch"],
    correct: " Participate",
  },
  {
    question: "	He said that he was <u>terrified</u> of tigers",
    choices: ["	Found", "	Shy", "	Very afraid", "	Tired"],
    correct: "	Very afraid",
  },
  {
    question: "	Some of the <u>regulations</u> seemed too severe",
    choices: ["	Judgements", " Rules", " Punishments", " Attitudes"],
    correct: " Rules",
  },
  {
    question: "	Tom cannot <u>afford</u> a new bicycle this year.",
    choices: [" Buy", "	Ride", "	Sell", "	Share"],
    correct: " Buy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	I wonder if you could <u>direct</u> me to Dr. Carmichael’s office?",
    choices: ["	Take", "	Bring", "	Tell………how to get", "	introduce"],
    correct: "	Tell………how to get",
  },
  {
    question: "	I knew my father would <u>discipline</u> me for my actions.",
    choices: ["	Reward", "	Congratulate", "	Praise", " Punish"],
    correct: " Punish",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	Look! The notice says quite clearly: “Smoking is __	forbidden in the theatre”",
    choices: ["	Strictly", "	Seriously", "	Exactly", "	Strongly"],
    correct: "	Strictly",
  },
  {
    question: "	She has a strange hobby. She____	poisonous snakes",
    choices: ["	Brings up", "	Grows", "	Cultivates", " Breeds"],
    correct: " Breeds",
  },
  {
    question: "	He emphasizes that ability at Maths is <u>essential.</u>",
    choices: ["	Excellent", "	Optional", "	Remarkable", " Necessary"],
    correct: " Necessary",
  },
  {
    question: "	I don’t know how she ___	a living as an artist",
    choices: ["	Does", " Earns", " Has", " Gets"],
    correct: " Earns",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	Her husband is very <u>competent</u>; he will repair the roof himself",
    choices: [" Capable", "	Industrious", "	Thrifty", "	Careful"],
    correct: " Capable",
  },
  {
    question: "	Today’s football match has been____	because of bad weather",
    choices: [" Postponed", "	Started", "	Decided", "	Put away"],
    correct: " Postponed",
  },
  {
    question: "	The show was dull, It was____________",
    choices: ["	Disinterested", "	Uninterested", "	Interesting", "	Uninteresting"],
    correct: "	Uninteresting",
  },
  {
    question: "	They	___ her on her new baby",
    choices: ["	Mentioned", "	Congratulated", "	Praised", "	Commented"],
    correct: "	Congratulated",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	Mona is the best student in the class. She is ___	to all other sudents",
    choices: ["	Preferable", " Superior", " Comparable", " Senior"],
    correct: " Superior",
  },
  {
    question: "	 	___  More help, I could call my neighbor",
    choices: ["	Needed", "	Should I need", "	I have needed", "	I should need"],
    correct: "	Should I need",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	Unless you __	all of my questions, I can’t do anything to help you",
    choices: ["	Answered", " Answer", " Would answer", "Are answering"],
    correct: " Answer",
  },
  {
    question: "Ask the watchman ___",
    choices: [
      "	Whose is this car",
      "	This is whose car",
      " Whose car that is",
      " Whose car is that",
    ],
    correct: " Whose car that is",
  },
  {
    question: "	To prepare for the TOEFL,___	thirty every day for several moths",
    choices: [" Study", "	Studying", "	To study", "	To have study"],
    correct: " Study",
  },
  {
    question: "	Out neighbours ___	their house painted once a year.",
    choices: ["	Make", " Have", " Do", " Fix"],
    correct: " Have",
  },
  {
    question: "	Promise me	___ lies again",
    choices: [
      " That you’ll never tell",
      "	Never tell",
      "	That you never tell",
      "	Never telling",
    ],
    correct: " That you’ll never tell",
  },
  {
    question: "	I must get	___ before the boss sees it,",
    choices: [
      "	My office tidying up",
      "	Tidied up my office",
      "	Tidying up my office",
      " My office tidied up",
    ],
    correct: " My office tidied up",
  },
  {
    question: "	“why don’t you emigrate to Australia?” “	___ “",
    choices: [
      " If only I could!",
      "	When I only could!",
      "	How I wish it!",
      "	I hope so!",
    ],
    correct: " If only I could!",
  },
  {
    question: "	Jan___	better take care. The roads are very busy",
    choices: ["	Was", "	Would", "	Should", " Had"],
    correct: " Had",
  },
  {
    question: "	 ___	would you solve the problem if this method failed?",
    choices: ["	What else", "	Who else", "	Whose else", " How else"],
    correct: " How else",
  },
  {
    question: "	It was difficult.	,___he managed to do it.",
    choices: [" However", "	But", "	Therefore", "	Moreover"],
    correct: " However",
  },
  {
    question: "	__ raise 860 million pounds, they increased tobacco duty",
    choices: ["	As to", "	In order as", "	So to", "	In order to"],
    correct: "	In order to",
  },
  {
    question: "	It’s not worth___out now. It is much too late.",
    choices: ["	To go", "	It go", " Going", " It going"],
    correct: " Going",
  },
  {
    question: "	I’m afraid you will___	wait a long time",
    choices: [" Have to", "	Must", "	Be to", "	Have got to"],
    correct: " Have to",
  },
  {
    question: "	Do you mind	___ the cooking?",
    choices: [" Doing", "	To do", "	For doing", "	To doing"],
    correct: " Doing",
  },
  {
    question: "	I shouted at him ___	dropping the ball",
    choices: ["	With", "	To", " For", " At"],
    correct: " For",
  },
  {
    question: "	She told ___	afraid",
    choices: ["	That she was", "	Us that she was", "	Us being", "	For being"],
    correct: "	Us that she was",
  },
  {
    question: "	Drinking __	one’s health",
    choices: [
      "	Can affect dangerously",
      " Can seriously affect",
      " Seriously can effect",
      " Seriously can endanger",
    ],
    correct: " Can seriously affect",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	Teenagers want to show they’re different,	____they react against their families",
    choices: ["	Because", "	But", "	So", "	Then"],
    correct: "	So",
  },
  {
    question: "	There are other drugs	___ alcohol and nicotine.",
    choices: ["	As well", "	Too", "	Besides", "	By"],
    correct: "	Besides",
  },
  {
    question: "	You can’t smoke in here. It’s___	the law",
    choices: ["	According", "	Anti", "	Against", "	Opposite"],
    correct: "	Against",
  },
  {
    question: "	Joe’s pants were torn	___up the tree",
    choices: [
      "	While climbing",
      "	In climbing",
      "	While he was climbing",
      "	Upon climbing",
    ],
    correct: "	While he was climbing",
  },
  {
    question: "	We haven’t seen you____________",
    choices: [
      "	in the past four years",
      "	since four years",
      "	last four years",
      "	four years ago",
    ],
    correct: "	in the past four years",
  },
  {
    question: "	I ‘d like ___	to think about it.",
    choices: [
      "	Little time",
      " A little time",
      " Sometime little",
      " Any little time",
    ],
    correct: " A little time",
  },
  {
    question: "	A lot of guests were expected, but___came",
    choices: [" Few", "	A few", "	Some few", "	Only some very few"],
    correct: " Few",
  },
  {
    question: "	I don’t know what’s the matter with me. I’m not ___	today",
    choices: ["	Me", "	Mine", "	Myself", "	I"],
    correct: "	Myself",
  },
  {
    question: "	Tom’all right__	but his wife is badly hurt",
    choices: [" Himself", "	With his self", "	By him", "	Oneself"],
    correct: " Himself",
  },
  {
    question: "	The club___	last year",
    choices: [
      " Was started",
      "	Had been started",
      "	Was being started",
      "	Has been started",
    ],
    correct: " Was started",
  },
  {
    question: "	You can stay here	______ you don’t make a loud noise",
    choices: ["	Otherwise", "	Until", "	Unless", "	So long as"],
    correct: "	So long as",
  },
  {
    question: "	Some of the boys__	didn’t come",
    choices: [
      "	Whom I invited them",
      "	I invited them",
      " I invited",
      " When I invited",
    ],
    correct: " I invited",
  },
  {
    question: "	The sky was overcast; it___",
    choices: [
      " Looked like rain",
      "	Looked like raining",
      "	Looked for rain",
      "	Looked for raining",
    ],
    correct: " Looked like rain",
  },
  {
    question: "	I will return your notes as soon as__-	copying them",
    choices: ["	I will finish", " I finish", " I finished", " I be finished"],
    correct: " I finish",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	The missing war correspondent was last seen yesterday morning____________ his Lan Rover near the frontline",
    choices: ["	Driving", "	As driving", "	To drive", "	Was driving"],
    correct: "	Driving",
  },
  {
    question: "	The vehicle was found yesterday evening but	___ no sign of him",
    choices: ["	There had", "	It was", "	It had", "	There was"],
    correct: "	There was",
  },
  {
    question: "	The hostesses had finished___the trays.",
    choices: [" Collecting", "	To collect", "	Collected", "	At collecting"],
    correct: " Collecting",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	“Did you see anyone interesting at the party?” “Yes,	____ were there”",
    choices: [
      "	Some of John’s friends",
      "	Some friend of John’s",
      "	Some of John’s friend",
      "	Some of John friends",
    ],
    correct: "	Some of John’s friends",
  },
  {
    question: "	“I don’t think I’ll ever understand algebra!” “Just keep on	___“",
    choices: ["	Tries", "	Try", "	To try", " Trying"],
    correct: " Trying",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	“The temperature has relly risen today” “Yes, it is___	I can’t work”",
    choices: ["	Too hot that", " So hot that", " Very hot that", " Hot that"],
    correct: " So hot that",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	___ On television can be very damaging to children who watch the programs.",
    choices: [
      "	The too great sex and violence",
      "	Sex and violence too much",
      "	The great numbers of sex and violence",
      " Too much sex and violence",
    ],
    correct: " Too much sex and violence",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	Tom and Bill were badly injured in the last match, so	___can play today",
    choices: [
      "	Both of them",
      "	Either one of them",
      " Neither of them",
      " Not any of them",
    ],
    correct: " Neither of them",
  },
  {
    question: " ____________	eight musicians in the band",
    choices: [
      "	They will consist",
      "	They ‘re being",
      "	There is",
      "	There will be",
    ],
    correct: "	There will be",
  },
  {
    question: "	He doesn’t know	___ about sports",
    choices: ["	Nothing", " Anything", " Things", " Something"],
    correct: " Anything",
  },
  {
    question: "	Alex could not start his car because____ 	",
    choices: [
      "	Of not knowing where to find his key",
      "	Where his key wad he didn’t know",
      " He didn’t know where his key was",
      " To find his key he did not know where",
    ],
    correct: " He didn’t know where his key was",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	If you need an extra bed for your guest, you can use one____________",
    choices: [" Of ours", "	Us", "	Ours", "	Of us"],
    correct: " Of ours",
  },
  {
    question: "	This toaster is____	as the one you bought at Mary’s",
    choices: [" Just as good", "	Equally as good", "	Good as", "	Equal as good"],
    correct: " Just as good",
  },
  {
    question: "	 	_______, Ruggiero Ricci was considered a great violinist",
    choices: [
      " At the age of six",
      "	At six of years old",
      "	When age six",
      "	When he was six years age",
    ],
    correct: " At the age of six",
  },
  {
    question: "	Where’sPolly? “She____________",
    choices: [
      "	Is in her room studying",
      "	In her room is studying",
      "	Studies in her room",
      "	Has in her room studies",
    ],
    correct: "	Is in her room studying",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	Fatemah looked down to discover a snake at her feet. When she saw it, she____________",
    choices: ["	Was screaming", "	Had screamed", " Screamed", "	Screams"],
    correct: " Screamed",
  },
  {
    question: "	The vegetables didn’t taste very good. They_____for too long",
    choices: [
      "	Had cooked",
      "	Had been cooking",
      "	Have been cooking",
      " Had been cooked",
    ],
    correct: " Had been cooked",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	Somebody is cleaning the room at the moment. The room	_____at the moment",
    choices: [
      "	Is being cleaning",
      "	Is cleaning",
      "	Is to be cleaned",
      " Is being cleaned",
    ],
    correct: " Is being cleaned",
  },
  {
    question: "	She admitted	____ the money",
    choices: ["	To steal", "	To have stolen", " Having stolen", " To be stolen"],
    correct: " Having stolen",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	________unprepared for the exam, I felt sure I would get a low score",
    choices: [" Being", "	Having", "	Because", "	Upon"],
    correct: " Being",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	The Council are planning to build four 20-storey_______of flats in the are",

    choices: ["	Masses", " Blocks", " Chunks", " Structures"],
    correct: " Blocks",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	They promised to give her a modern flat which is_______for an elderly person living alone.",
    choices: ["	Top", "	Utmost", "	Foremost", " Ideal"],
    correct: " Ideal",
  },
  {
    question: "	The inpector said that there was not much____of an explosion",
    choices: ["	Display", "	Signal", "	Evidence", "	Mark"],
    correct: "	Evidence",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	In the English Channel, the “ Mary Celeste”	____with another ship, which sank.",
    choices: ["	Bumped", "	Struck", " Collided", " Stuck"],
    correct: " Collided",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	When the “Mary Celeste,” did not____	his signal, Captain Moorhouse decided to investigate.",
    choices: ["	Answer", "	Respond", "	Retrace", "	Retain"],
    correct: "	Answer",
  },
  {
    question: "	Drivers have now been forbidden to ___	up hitchhikers",
    choices: [" Pick", "	Put", "	Pull", "	Get"],
    correct: " Pick",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	Dr. Carmichael had been looking	_____ to meeting his new research assistant",
    choices: ["	Through	", " forward	", " across	", "on"],
    correct: " forward	",
  },
  {
    question:
      "She …............. French before she began studying English in 1990.",
    choices: ["A. had studied", "B. studied", "C. studies", "D. has studied"],
    correct: "A. had studied",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Children in large families learn how to get …............. with other people.",
    choices: ["A. along", "B. away", "C. cross", "D. through"],
    correct: "A. along",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question: "Are you coming on the ……………… to Cairo today?",
    choices: ["A. excursion", "B. exploration", "C. mission", "D. taste"],
    correct: "A. excursion",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question: "Please wait for him …............. he comes back.",
    choices: ["A. when", "B. so", "C. for", "D. until"],
    correct: "D. until",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question: "We would …............. to stay at home this evening.",
    choices: ["A. approve", "B. recommend", "C. prefer", "D. rather"],
    correct: "C. prefer",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question: "I don’t like …............. with strangers.",
    choices: ["A. talked", "B. to talk", "C. talk", "D. talking"],
    correct: "D. talking",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question: "I have never ……………… any experience of living in the country.",
    choices: ["A. had", "B. wished", "C. done", "D. made"],
    correct: "A. had",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question: "Do you like this suit? I’ve ……………… a friend of mine.",
    choices: [
      "A. lent it of",
      "B. lent it from",
      "C. borrowed",
      "D. borrowed it from",
    ],
    correct: "D. borrowed it from",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "John and Barbara …............. to get married in St Mark’s church.",
    choices: ["A. selected", "B. picked", "C. judged", "D. decided"],
    correct: "D. decided",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question: "A milkman is a man who ……………… milk.",
    choices: ["A. gives", "B. delivers", "C. buys", "D. sells"],
    correct: "D. sells",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question: "A milkman is a man who ……………… milk.",
    choices: ["A. gives", "B. delivers", "C. buys", "D. sells"],
    correct: "D. sells",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question: "1.She is too young …............. it",
    choices: [
      "A.to understand",
      "B.understanding",
      "C.understand",
      "D.understood",
    ],
    correct: "A.to understand",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "2.Her parents were very ……………… because she was out so late that night.",
    choices: ["A.responsible", "B.sorry", "C.worried", "D.overcome"],
    correct: "C.worried",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question: "3.I have seen him ….............",
    choices: [
      "A.ten days",
      "B.for ten days",
      "C.ten days ago",
      "D.in ten days",
    ],
    correct: "B.for ten days",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question: "4.It may be raining, but I’m thoroughly enjoying_____.",
    choices: ["A. himself", "B. yourself", "C. by myself", "D. myself"],
    correct: "D. myself",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question: "5.They will now have a …............. rest",
    choices: ["A.small", "B.little", "C.light", "D.short"],
    correct: "D.short",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "6.The librarian went to look in the cupboard …............. rare books were kept",
    choices: ["A.which", "B.where", "C.that", "D.there"],
    correct: "B.where",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question: "7.Drive fast ________ we will miss the train.",
    choices: ["A. because", "B. so", "C. although", "D. or"],
    correct: "D. or",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question: "8.Show me …............. my room, please?",
    choices: ["A.to", "B.of", "C.where", "D.on"],
    correct: "A.to",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question: "9.I’d like ……………… two seats in the circle, please",
    choices: ["A.booking", "B.to book", "C.booked", "D.book"],
    correct: "B.to book",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question: "10.He has just arrived …............. London.",
    choices: ["A.at", "B.in", "C.for", "D.to"],
    correct: "B.in",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "1.Although their carpets ___ primarily for mosques, sometimes, they ___ designs for restaurants and hotels as well.",
    choices: [
      "A. are designed – produce",
      "B.have been designed - were produced",
      "C.will be designed - were producing",
      "D.have designed - had been producing",
    ],
    correct: "A. are designed – produce",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "2.If the tree hadn't been so high, he ___ up to take his kite down.",
    choices: [
      "A.can climb",
      "B.could climb",
      "C.could have climbed",
      "D.was able to climb",
    ],
    correct: "C.could have climbed",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "3.Since, at the very beginning, he showed some inclination towards laziness, he ___ of all his duties. Afterwards he worked very well.",
    choices: [
      "A.had to be reminded",
      "B.had to remind",
      "C.must have reminded",
      "D.must have been reminded",
    ],
    correct: "A.had to be reminded",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "4.When Tiger Woods ___ his sixth golfing title in a row, he equalled the record of Ben Hogen, which ___ 52 years ago.",
    choices: [
      "A.has won - had set",
      "B.won - was set",
      "C.is won - had been set",
      "D.wins - has been set",
    ],
    correct: "B.won - was set",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "5.I'm not sure who should be punished for the incident. Certainly not Alice, since she ___ of possible dangers.",
    choices: [
      "A.wasn't warned",
      "B.hasn't warned",
      "C.hadn't warned",
      "D.wouldn't be warned",
    ],
    correct: "A.wasn't warned",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question: "6.If eating disorders ___, they can be fatal.",
    choices: [
      "A.aren't treating",
      "B.aren't treated",
      "C.weren't treated",
      "D.don't treat",
    ],
    correct: "B.aren't treated",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "7.Usually I ___ cash for things because I ___ using credit cards.",
    choices: [
      "A.have paid - didn't like",
      "B.pay - don't like",
      "C.have been paid - won't like",
      "D.am paying - haven't liked",
    ],
    correct: "B.pay - don't like",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "8.The origin of April Fool's Day, the first day of April, is uncertain, but it ___ to arrival of spring in late March, when nature ___ to 'fool' humanity with changes in weather.",
    choices: [
      "A.has been related - has said",
      "B.may be related - is said",
      "C.ought to relate - has been said",
      "D.relates - is saying",
    ],
    correct: "B.may be related - is said",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "9.This morning, the attendant ___ a baby who ___ in an old blanket on the steps of the country hospital.",
    choices: [
      "A.finds – wrapped",
      "B.was being found - has been wrapped",
      "C.found - was wrapped",
      "D.was found - had been wrapped",
    ],
    correct: "C.found - was wrapped",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "10.It's true that life ___ as anything may happen at any time, but some precautions such as insurance policies, ___ against disaster.",
    choices: [
      "A.mustn't be predicted - have taken",
      "B.shouldn't predict - have been taking",
      "C.doesn't predict - are taking",
      "D.can't be predicted - can be taken",
    ],
    correct: "D.can't be predicted - can be taken",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question: "1.He is coming ______ a cold after a night out in the rain.",
    choices: ["A. down with", "B. up with", "C. away from", "D. across with"],
    correct: "A. down with",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question: "2.Although his work is not outstanding it is………….. done.",
    choices: ["A. enough", "B. sufficient", "C. well", "D. adequate"],
    correct: "C. well",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "3.We must push the piano to the corner of the hall to ______ our party tonight.",
    choices: [
      "A. make place for",
      "B. take up room to",
      "C. make room for",
      "D. give place to",
    ],
    correct: "C. make room for",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question: "4.Thang: 'What do you think about the novel?' Huong: '______'",
    choices: [
      "A. Yes, let's.",
      "B. The best I've ever read!",
      "C. I can't agree with you more.",
      "D. I wish I could.",
    ],
    correct: "B. The best I've ever read!",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "5.The women who…. next door is often willing to help us whenever we are in difficulty.",
    choices: ["A. to live", "B. living", "C. lived", "D. lives"],
    correct: "D. lives",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "6.My favourite team ______ 15 games so far this season, and will probably win the championship.",
    choices: ["A. are winning", "B. won", "C. have won", "D. will win"],
    correct: "C. have won",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "7.______ John Kennedy was elected president, he was the youngest American President ever.",
    choices: ["A. When", "B. While", "C. Before", "D. As long as"],
    correct: "A. When",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "8.'The inflation rate in Greece is five times ______ my country,' he said.",
    choices: [
      "A. as much as",
      "B. more than",
      "C. as many as that in",
      "D. as high as that in",
    ],
    correct: "D. as high as that in",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question: "I’m not accustomed ___ up so early.",
    choices: ["A. to getting", "B. to get", "C. by getting", "D. get"],
    correct: "A. to getting",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "10.The ………….. charged by the architect for the plans of the new building were unusually high.",
    choices: ["A. hire", "B. price", "C. fees", "D. sum"],
    correct: "C. fees",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "1.George has been in the publishing business since he ______ college.",
    choices: ["was in", "learned", "had in", "worked"],
    correct: "was in",
  },
  {
    question: "2.I don’t know where …............. before he came here.",
    choices: ["is he living", "he had lived", "did he live", "has he lived"],
    correct: "he had lived",
  },
  {
    question: "3.Mr. and Mrs. Kent are old age ………………",
    choices: ["workers", "people", "folks", "pensioners"],
    correct: "pensioners",
  },
  {
    question:
      "4.My aunt and uncle always quarreled about their tea; she like it strong but he wanted it….............",
    choices: ["feeble", "weak", "small", "poor"],
    correct: "weak",
  },
  {
    question:
      "5.How much are the tickets? 'I think they are two dollars ………………'",
    choices: ["one", "every", "each", "much"],
    correct: "each",
  },
  {
    question: "6.It is such a big city that he’s got ….............",
    choices: ["late", "loose", "lost", "up"],
    correct: "lost",
  },
  {
    question: "7.Will you ……………… me to post this letter tomorrow?",
    choices: ["remember", "mind", "suggest", "remind"],
    correct: "remind",
  },
  {
    question: "8.Show me …............. my room, please?",
    choices: ["to", "of", "where", "on"],
    correct: "where",
  },
  {
    question:
      "9.…............. he joined the army my brother had never been abroad",
    choices: ["Since", "While", "During", "Until"],
    correct: "Until",
  },
  {
    question: "10.006, the secret agent, is on an important ………………",
    choices: ["job", "work", "mission", "tap"],
    correct: "mission",
  },
  {
    question:
      "1.Her career was all ___ she cared about, ___ made her so successful.",
    choices: ["what – which", "what – that", "that – that", "that – which"],
    correct: "what – that",
  },
  {
    question:
      "2.___ I wear tonight depends on ___ you're planning to take me to. Shall I wear something special, or should I dress more casually?",
    choices: ["What – where", "How – when", "If – what", "Which - how"],
    correct: "What – where",
  },
  {
    question:
      "3.To achieve the unique coral red of the Ottoman tiles in the 16th century, ___ craftsmen a mixture of iron-oxide and quartz.",
    choices: ["have fired", "were fired", "used to fire", "could be fired"],
    correct: "used to fire",
  },
  {
    question:
      "4.The moment that the sun reappears just ___ a total solar eclipse is known as a 'diamond ring'.",
    choices: ["as soon as", "when", "before", "after"],
    correct: "after",
  },
  {
    question: "5.Asthma is a lung disease which ___.",
    choices: [
      "it makes difficult to breathe",
      "makes it difficult to breathe",
      "makes it difficult breathing",
      "makes difficult to breathe",
    ],
    correct: "makes it difficult to breathe",
  },
  {
    question:
      "6.Without washing machines; vacuum cleaners, etc., it ___ impossible for us to have as much leisure time as we now do.",
    choices: ["has been", "should be", "will be", "would be"],
    correct: "would be",
  },
  {
    question:
      "7.It was so embarrassing; I really wish I ___ her name when I met her again last night.",
    choices: [
      "hadn't forgotten",
      "haven't forgotten",
      "wouldn't forget",
      "didn't forget",
    ],
    correct: "hadn't forgotten",
  },
  {
    question:
      "8.Emma has got a cat flap put in her balcony door ___ she doesn't always have to open the door to let her cat in and out.",
    choices: ["nonetheless", "in order that", "whenever", "as though"],
    correct: "in order that",
  },
  {
    question:
      "9.I have bought ___ new shirt which matches ___ jacket I bought last week.",
    choices: ["some – a", "the – a", "a – the", "some - the"],
    correct: "a – the",
  },
  {
    question:
      "10.Most critics agree that rather little ___ done by the artist after his illness has any great value.",
    choices: [
      "of what was",
      "of that was",
      "of that what was",
      "which has been",
    ],
    correct: "of what was",
  },
  {
    question:
      "1.I ____ hope there won’t be a repetition of these unfortunate events.",
    choices: ["deeply", "strongly", "sincerely", "thoroughly"],
    correct: "sincerely",
  },
  {
    question:
      "2.After thirty-five years in the French department, Professor Lane finally _____ last month.",
    choices: ["withdrew", "retired", "treated", "abdicated"],
    correct: "retired",
  },
  {
    question: "3.The contract was ……………… at lunchtime.",
    choices: ["signed", "decided", "delivered", "agreed"],
    correct: "signed",
  },
  {
    question: "4.It is such a big city that he’s got ….............",
    choices: ["late", "loose", "lost", "up"],
    correct: "lost",
  },
  {
    question:
      "5.He’s very _____ about his work, so try not to say anything that he might take as a criticism.",
    choices: ["annoyed", "touchy", "irritated", "annoying"],
    correct: "annoyed",
  },
  {
    question: "6.Show me …............. my room, please?",
    choices: ["to", "of", "where", "on"],
    correct: "to",
  },
  {
    question:
      "7.Listen to that music! Our neighbors _____ play music that loud at this hour.",
    choices: ["should", "shouldn’t", "can", "cannot"],
    correct: "shouldn’t",
  },
  {
    question:
      "8.Deforestation ______ an alarming decrease in the amount of farming land.",
    choices: ["are", "was", "is", "were"],
    correct: "is",
  },
  {
    question:
      "9.If we behave badly in class, our teacher ____ stay late and do extra work.",
    choices: ["much", "lets us", "allows us to", "makes us"],
    correct: "makes us",
  },
  {
    question: "10.Mr. and Mrs. Kent are old age ………………",
    choices: ["workers", "people", "folks", "pensioners"],
    correct: "pensioners",
  },
  {
    question:
      "1. Well, as long as Mr. Idiot ___ to say things we might find embarrassing, his presence is not a problem.",
    choices: ["won't lead", "won't be led", "isn't led", "doesn't lead"],
    correct: "isn't led",
  },
  {
    question:
      "2. What? Your sister saw Jimmy at The Oasis! Well, if it ___ him, he must have been dismissed again.",
    choices: [
      "were really",
      "was really",
      "had really been",
      "really had been",
    ],
    correct: "was really",
  },
  {
    question:
      "3. If the M1 motorway ___ , the traffic in London ___ to a standstill.",
    choices: [
      "wasn't built - should have come",
      "isn't going to be built - comes",
      "hadn't been built - would have come",
      "won't be built - has come",
    ],
    correct: "hadn't been built - would have come",
  },
  {
    question:
      "4. Don't regret you couldn't come. Your arrival ___ my decision.",
    choices: [
      "wouldn't have changed",
      "wouldn't change",
      "may not have changed",
      "couldn't change",
    ],
    correct: "wouldn't have changed",
  },
  {
    question: "5.Are you sure my tablecloth ___ permanently by this red wine?",
    choices: [
      "won't be stained",
      "isn't being stained",
      "won't stain",
      "shouldn't have stained",
    ],
    correct: "won't be stained",
  },
  {
    question:
      "6.At the end of the training session, you ___ a test. Students who pass ___ to scuba dive in the open seas.",
    choices: [
      "are given - have allowed",
      "will be given - will be allowed",
      "have given - have been allowed",
      "had been giving - are allowed",
    ],
    correct: "will be given - will be allowed",
  },
  {
    question:
      "7. Mr. Grunfeld ___ for his humour already, but on this occasion the whole class ___ hysterically.",
    choices: [
      "knew - had been laughing",
      "was known - laugh",
      "has known – laughed",
      "is known - was laughing",
    ],
    correct: "is known - was laughing",
  },
  {
    question: "8.Recently, a new vaccine against measles ___ .",
    choices: [
      "has been developed",
      "had been developed",
      "had developed",
      "was developing",
    ],
    correct: "has been developed",
  },
  {
    question:
      "9.Dogs, which ___ man since ancient times, were mainly used on farms or for hunting in earlier times, but today they ___ to a wide range of uses, such as drug or victim detection.",
    choices: [
      "accompany - are being put",
      "have accompanied - are put",
      "had been accompanying - are putting",
      "were accompanying - put",
    ],
    correct: "have accompanied - are put",
  },
  {
    question:
      "10.There is no point asking Bob for information concerning the contest. As far as I know he ___ about it.",
    choices: [
      "hasn't been told",
      "didn't tell",
      "hasn't told",
      "wouldn't tell",
    ],
    correct: "hasn't been told",
  },
  {
    question: "1.I’m sorry we’re late; it’s all my ….............!",
    choices: ["guilt", "crime", "fault", "wrong"],
    correct: "fault",
  },
  {
    question:
      "2.He is ____by many people for the money he has helped raise for charity.",
    choices: ["admired", "regarded", "approved", "considered"],
    correct: "admired",
  },
  {
    question:
      "3.Her parents were very ……………… because she was out so late that night.",
    choices: ["responsible", "sorry", "worried", "overcome"],
    correct: "worried",
  },
  {
    question:
      "4.We flew to the island, then ……………… a car for three days and visited most places of interest.",
    choices: ["lent", "bought", "hired", "changed"],
    correct: "hired",
  },
  {
    question:
      "5.Children in large families learn how to get …............. with other people.",
    choices: ["along", "away", "cross", "through"],
    correct: "along",
  },
  {
    question: "6.The teacher told them answer ……………… the question.",
    choices: ["of", "for", "in", "to"],
    correct: "to",
  },
  {
    question:
      "7.He returned to his home town ___ he spent the rest of his life.",
    choices: ["that", "which", "where", "who"],
    correct: "where",
  },
  {
    question: "8.Show me …............. my room, please?",
    choices: ["to", "of", "where", "on"],
    correct: "to",
  },
  {
    question:
      "9.My aunt and uncle always quarreled about their tea; she liked it strong but he wanted it….............",
    choices: ["feeble", "weak", "small", "poor"],
    correct: "weak",
  },
  {
    question:
      "10.The author ______ that it is necessary for every adolescent to establish his own place in society.",
    choices: ["believes", "believed", "believed", "has believed"],
    correct: "believes",
  },
  {
    question: "1.Are you sure we are going in the right _____?",
    choices: ["direct", "direction", "directed", "directly"],
    correct: "direction",
  },
  {
    question: "2.My new car is more _____ than the one I had before.",
    choices: ["economy", "economical", "economic", "economics"],
    correct: "economical",
  },
  {
    question: "3.I ____ doubt whether he will actually carry out his threats.",
    choices: ["highly", "deeply", "absolutely", "seriously"],
    correct: "deeply",
  },
  {
    question:
      "4.She was very_____and told me quite simply that she didn’t like me.",
    choices: ["genuine", "open", "blunt", "sincere"],
    correct: "blunt",
  },
  {
    question:
      "5.We can win only if we remain united, and so we must support them the moment they ____ on strike.",
    choices: ["are", "is", "was", "were"],
    correct: "are",
  },
  {
    question:
      "6.We ____at about seven o’clock this morning and we eventually arrived at half past four.",
    choices: ["set in", "set to", "set up", "set out"],
    correct: "set up",
  },
  {
    question:
      "7.We have to complete the film this month. No matter how cold it ____, all the summer scenes will have to be shot tomorrow.",
    choices: ["would be", "will be", "is", "were"],
    correct: "is",
  },
  {
    question: "8.Everybody ____ here except for Jill two hours ago.",
    choices: ["is", "was", "has been", "had been"],
    correct: "had been",
  },
  {
    question: "9.The Boston police went on ____in 1919.",
    choices: ["operation", "set up", "strike", "join"],
    correct: "strike",
  },
  {
    question:
      "10.Lizzie should ask Bryan to help her with her studies. He did the ____ course last year.",
    choices: ["of", "like", "same", "as"],
    correct: "same",
  },
];
function shuffleArray(quizEnglish1) {
  for (let i = 0; i < quizEnglish1.length; i += 1) {
    const group = quizEnglish1.slice(i, i + 1);
    for (let j = group.length - 1; j > 0; j--) {
      const randomIndex = Math.floor(Math.random() * (j + 1));
      [group[j], group[randomIndex]] = [group[randomIndex], group[j]];
    }
    quizEnglish1.splice(10);
  }
}
shuffleArray(quizEnglish1);
export { quizEnglish1 };
